Till death do us part
The Russian Bride is a horror, thriller film directed by Michael S. Ojeda.
A Russian woman travels to America with her daughter to marry a reclusive billionaire offering them a better life,
but soon begins to suspect her new husband might have a far more sinister plan for their arrangement.
Karl Frederick, played by Corbin Bernsen.
Nina, played by Oksana Orlan.
Dasha, played by Kristina Pimenova.
Keller, played by Gregory O'Gallagher.
Lucia, played by Yuliya Zelenskaya.
Maria, played by Lisa Goodman.
The Princess Bride is a 1987 American fantasy adventure comedy film directed and co-produced by Rob Reiner and starring Cary Elwes, Robin Wright,
Mandy Patinkin, André the Giant, Chris Sarandon, Christopher Guest, Wallace Shawn, Peter Falk, Fred Savage, Billy Crystal and Carol Kane.
Adapted by William Goldman from his novel of the same name, it tells the story of a swashbuckling farmhand named Westley, accompanied by
companions befriended along the way, who must rescue his true love Princess Buttercup from the odious Prince Humperdinck.
The film preserves the novel's metafictional narrative style by presenting the
story as a book being read by a grandfather to his sick grandson.
The film was first released by 20th Century Fox in the United States and by Interaccess Film Distribution
in international markets on September 25, 1987, and received widespread critical acclaim.
After having only modest initial box office success, it has over time become a cult film and gained
recognition as one of the greatest films of the 1980s as well as one of Reiner's best works.
The film is number 50 on the Bravo's "100 Funniest Movies", number 88 on The American Film Institute's (AFI) "AFI's 100
Years...100 Passions" list of the 100 greatest film love stories, and 46 in Channel 4's 50 Greatest Comedy Films list.
The film also won the 1988 Hugo Award for Best Dramatic Presentation.
The film also won the People's Choice Award at the 12th
Toronto International Film Festival.
In 2016, the film was selected by the Library of Congress for preservation in the United States
National Film Registry as being "culturally, historically or aesthetically significant".
The film explores themes of winter, psychopath,
snowstorm, bride, mail order bride.
The tone is dark and intense.